<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects | Seongheon Park</title><link>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/</link><atom:link href="https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Projects</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://seongheon-park.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Projects</title><link>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/</link></image><item><title>Development of Multimodal-based General-purpose Social Artificial Intelligence Technology</title><link>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project4/</guid><description>&lt;p>Research on artificial intelligence technology that can mimic various human abilities by using image/video, voice/audio, and text/natural language, which are the basis of artificial intelligence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Complex and comprehensive scene understanding using multimodal signals, user understanding, virtual space-time synthesis technology, and development of a general-purpose social artificial intelligence system through the integration of these technologies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Development of Complex Situational Awareness and Prediction Technology through Multi-modal Data Fusion and Social Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project3/</guid><description>&lt;p>Developing source technology for complext scene understanding and future prediction through artificial intelligence neural networks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Integrating complementary information in multiple ways through convergence between multimodal data.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Describing human social intelligence to develop complex relationship reasoning skills bewteen multiple objects and surrounding environments through learning of a social AI.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Deep Identification and Tracking of Missing Persons in Heterogeneous CCTV</title><link>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seongheon-park.github.io/project/project1/</guid><description>&lt;p>Developing artificial intelligence/machine learning source technology through future situation prediction research through human-like comprehensive video understanding.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Comprehensive video understanding includes contextual information through correlation analysis between human emotion/action/surrounding scene.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Development of emotion recognition technology through video-based interaction of emotion/action/environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Development of human-centric comprehensive video scene analysis and action recognition technology.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Development of environmental change prediction technology through comprehensive situational recognition.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>